Guide to George Mason University Faculty Course Evaluations
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
George Mason University Faculty Course Evaluations
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
GMU 003
47 cubic feet (70.5 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open to research.
Scope and Content Information
This series of the George Mason University Archives group contains the tabulated results of semester faculty course evaluations administered by the University administration. These materials record the total ratings given GMU instructors by students who had taken their courses.
Arrangement
Arranged by Year/Semester/Discipline or Department/Course Number/Section.
Contents List
- GMU Archives- Faculty/Course Evaluations
  - English- History- Y [Undated] (Box Box 131)
  - Nursing- Public Affairs- Y [Undated] (Box Box 131)
  - Business Admin.- Education- Z [Undated] (Box Box 131)
  - Fine/Perform- Mathematics- Z [Undated] (Box Box 131)
  - Phil. and Reli.- Sociology- Z [Undated] (Box Box 131)
  - Biology- Education- X [Undated] (Box Box 130)
  - English- General Studies- X [Undated] (Box Box 130)
  - Health and Physical Ed.- Physics- X [Undated] (Box Box 130)
  - Psychology- Sociology- X [Undated] (Box Box 130)
  - Biology- Economics- Y [Undated] (Box Box 130)
  - History and Art History- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Institute for Computational SCI and Informatics- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Institute of the Arts- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Mathematical Studies- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Modern and Classical Languages- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Music- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - New Century College- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Development- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Office of the Dean (Box Box 129)
  - Office of the Provost (Box Box 129)
  - Operations Research and Engineering- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Page Program- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Physics- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Psychology (Box Box 129)
  - Public and International Affairs- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - School of Law- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - School of Management- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Study of the Americas- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Telecommunications- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - The Institute of Public Policy- Spring 1998 (Box Box 129)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Biology- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Center for Community College Education- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Communication- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Division of Dance- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Division of Studio Art- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Division of Theater- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Economics- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - English- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Sciences- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Graduate School of Education- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Health and Human Services- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - History and Art History- Spring 1998 (Box Box 128)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Fall 1997 (Box Box 127)
  - Study of the Americas- Fall 1997 (Box Box 127)
  - Systems Engineering- Fall 1997 (Box Box 127)
  - The Institute of Public Policy- Fall 1997 (Box Box 127)
  - School of Management- Fall 1997 (Box Box 127)
  - Music- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - New Century College- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Office of Adult Hearing and Professional Dev. (Box Box 126)
  - Office of the Dean, CAS- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Office of the Dean, SITE- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Office of the Provost- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Operations Research and Engineering- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Page Program- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Physics- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Psychology- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - School of Law- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - Public and International Affairs- Fall 1997 (Box Box 126)
  - English- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Sciences- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Graduate School of Education- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Health and Human Services- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - History and Art History- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Institute for Computational SCI and Informatics- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Institute of the Arts- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Liberal Studies- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Modern and Classical Languages- Fall 1997 (Box Box 125)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Biology- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Center for Community College Education- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Communication- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Division of Dance- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Division of Studio Art- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Division of Theater- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Economics- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1997 (Box Box 124)
  - Mathematics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Medical Technology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Music- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - New Century Learning Communities- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - New Professional Studies, Teaching, MA- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Nursing- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Operations Research- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Page Program- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Parks, Recreation and Leisure Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Philosophy- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Physical Education- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Physics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Psychology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Public Administration- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Public Policy- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Reading- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Religious Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Russian- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Social Work- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Sociology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Spanish- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Special Education- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Statistics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Study of the Americas- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Telecommunications- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Theatre- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - University Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Urban Systems Engineering- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Visual Information Technologies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Women's Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 123)
  - Education Research- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Engineering- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - English Advanced Composition (College of Nursing and Health Science)- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - English- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Environmental Studies and Public Policy- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Exercise Fitness and Health Promotion- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Finance- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Foreign Language- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - French- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Geography- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Geology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - German- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Government- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Health- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Health Science- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - History- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Information Systems- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Information Technology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - International Transactions- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Latin- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Law- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Learning- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Marketing- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Management- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Management Information System- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Master of Business Administration- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Master of Science in Taxation- Spring 1997 (Box Box 122)
  - Accounting- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Administration of Justice- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Art History- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Art Institute- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Art Studio- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Astronomy- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Anthropology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Biology- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Business Legal Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Classics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Communications- Fall 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Community College Education- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Computational Science and Informatics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Counseling and Development- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Cultural Studies- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Curriculum and Instruction- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Dance- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Economics- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Education- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Educational Instructional Technology (Box Box 121)
  - Education Leadership- Spring 1997 (Box Box 121)
  - Accounting and Business Legal Studies- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Art History- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Biology- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Chemistry- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Decision Sciences and MGMT Information Systems- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Communications- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Computer Science- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Division of Dance- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Division of Studio Art- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Division of Theater- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Economics- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - English- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Foreign Languages and Literature- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Finance- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Sciences- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Graduate School of Education- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Health and Human Services- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - History- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Information and Software System Engineering- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Inst. of Graduate and Prof. Business Studies- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Institute for Computational SCI and Informatics- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - International Institute- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Marketing- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Management- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Music- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Dev.- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Operations Research and Engineering- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Prince William Institute- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Psychology- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Public and International Affairs- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - School of Law- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - The Institute of Public Policy- Summer 1996 (Box Box 120)
  - Accounting- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Art History- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Biology- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Center for Community Education- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Communications- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Decision Sciences and MGMT Information Systems- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Division of Dance- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Division of Studio Art- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Division of Theater- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Economics- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - English- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Finance- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Foreign Languages and Literature- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Geography and Earth System Sciences- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Graduate School of Education- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Health and Human Services- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - History- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Information and Software System Engineering- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Institute for Computational SCI and Informatics- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Institute of the Arts- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Marketing- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution (Box Box 119)
  - International Institute- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Management- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Mathematical Science- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Music- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - New Century College- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Dev.- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Office of the Dean, CAS- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Office of the Provost- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Operations Research and Engineering- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Page Program- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Prince William Institute- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Psychology- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Public and International Affairs- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Physics- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - School of Law (Box Box 119)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Study of the Americas- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - The Institute of Public Policy- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Telecommunications- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - University Scholars Program- Spring 1996 (Box Box 119)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Psychology- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Physics- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Public and International Affairs- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - School of Law- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Study of the Americas- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Systems Engineering- Fall 1995 (Box Box 118)
  - Finance- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Foreign Languages and Literature- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Sciences- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Graduate School of Education- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - HESC- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Health Sciences- Health Sports and Leisure Studs- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - History- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Individualized Study- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Institute of the Arts- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Institute for Educational Transformation- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Institute of Public Policy- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - International Institute- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Liberal Studies- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Management- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Marketing- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Music- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Institute for Computational SCI and Informatics- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Dev.- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Office of the Provost- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Office of the Dean, CAS- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Operations Research and Engineering- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Office of the Dean, SITE- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Page Program- Fall 1995 (Box Box 117)
  - Accounting and Business Administration- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Art History- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Biology- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Center for Community College Education- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Communications- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Decision Sciences and MGMT Information Systems- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Division of Dance (Box Box 116)
  - Division of Studio Art- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Division of Theater- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Economics- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - English- Fall 1995 (Box Box 116)
  - Nursing- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Operations Research and Applied Statistics- Spring 1995 (Box Box 15)
  - Page Program- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Physics- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Psychology- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Institute for Public Policy- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Health Sciences- Social Work- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Theater- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - Individualized Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 115)
  - English- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Finance- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Foreign Language and Literature- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Sciences- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Health Sciences- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - History- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Inst. for Computational Sciences and Informatics (Box Box 114)
  - Institute of the Arts- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - International Institute- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - School of Law- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Management- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Marketing- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Music- Spring 1995 (Box Box 114)
  - Accounting and Business Legal Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - American Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Art History- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Studio Art- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Biology- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Chemistry-Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Center for Community College Education- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Communications- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Dance- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Decision Sciences and Information Systems- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Economics- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Education- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 113)
  - Biology- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Dance- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Decision Sciences and Mgmt Information Systems- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Graduate School of Education- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Dev.- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - English- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Foreign Languages and Literature- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Health Sciences- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Individualized Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Psychology- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Public and International Affairs- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Program for Social Organizational Learning- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Systems Engineering- Spring 1995 (Box Box 112)
  - Music- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Nursing Continuing Education- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Office of Adult Learning and Professional Development- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Office of the Dean, CAS- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Office of the Dean, SITE- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Office of the Provost- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Operations Research and Applied Statistics- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Page Program- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Philosophy and Religious Studies- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Program for Social and Organizational Learning- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Psychology- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Physics- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Public and International Affairs- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - School of Law- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Sociology and Anthropology- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Studio Art- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Systems Engineering- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - Theater- Fall 1994 (Box Box 111)
  - English- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Finance- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Foreign Languages and Literature- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Geography and Earth Systems Science- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Exercise Science and Health- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Health Science- Health Sports and Leisure Studies- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Health Sciences- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Health Science- Social Work- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - History- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Individualized Studies- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Information and Software Systems Engineering- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Institute for Public Policy- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Institute of the Arts- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - International Institute- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Liberal Studies- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Management- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Marketing- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Fall 1994 (Box Box 110)
  - Accounting and Business Legal Studies- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Applied and Engineering Statistics- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Art History- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Biology- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Center for Community College Education- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - College of Nursing and Health Science- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Communications- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Institute for Computational Sciences and Informatics- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Dance- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Decision Sciences and Management Information Systems- Fall 1994, Folder 12 (Box Box 109)
  - Economics- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)
  - Graduate School of Education- Fall 1994 (Box Box 109)